Contact

palaktuteja11@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/palak-tuteja-3a3863165 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Research

Communication

Finance

Languages

English (Full Professional)

Honors-Awards

1st position in Mock Stock
Academic Excellence certificate
1st position in Group Discussion
2nd position in Marketing planning
competition

3rd position in Public Relations Competition

Palak Tuteja

Freelancer | Digital Marketer | Brand Strategist | Trader New Delhi

Summary

I'm curious, highly motivated Digital Marketer. I have done research to find the algorithmic interest to target the cold audience. I specialise in facebook advertisements. have also started my YouTube channel in which I explain about various National level exams which are conducted and I give tips on how to clear those exams. I like to face different kinds of challenges and I am very much inclined towards social welfare cause. I have gained some experience in various fields like marketing and research.

I love to explore new things and like facing different challenges.

Experience

Freelance
Digital Marketing
January 2020 - Present (8 months)

auctera™ Digital Marketer June 2020 - August 2020 (3 months)

NNEELL'S INVEST
Partner
January 2020 - August 2020 (8 months)

Confederation Of Young Leaders (CYL)
Public Policy Research Associate
April 2020 - May 2020 (2 months)

Findicate, the Finance Society of Kamala Nehru College Vice President
August 2019 - April 2020 (9 months)

I post finance facts and relevant news related to finance daily on our social media handles to spread financial literacy. Manage the funds we receive to conduct the events in our college and conduct various finance related competitions every month.

Agdova Technologies
Business Development Analyst
January 2020 - March 2020 (3 months)

The Financial Doctors

Financial Market Trainee & Technical Strategy Developer Intern April 2019 - October 2019 (7 months)

I learned about various technical tools that can be used while evaluating charts. I compared different trading strategies and developed my own technical trading strategies and applied them in the financial market.

Commcentric, the Commerce Association of Kamala Nehru college Joint Secretary

September 2018 - August 2019 (1 year)

I handled 13 teams and socities (200+ students). Organized various inter college and intra College events throughout the year and was able to get sponsorship in cash as well as in kind.

Findicate, the Finance Society of Kamala Nehru College Associate

August 2017 - May 2018 (10 months)

Conducted a Mock Stock and managed the funds received for various events which were held throughout the year.

Jesus and Mary College, University of Delhi Campus Ambassador December 2017 - February 2018 (3 months)

Helped in promoting the annual event organised by JMC in my campus.

Enactus Sri Venkateswara College Marketing Analyst October 2017 - November 2017 (2 months)

Researched and gathered information to make a plan to help in doing promotion effectively.

Qrius (formerly The Indian Economist) 3 months

Marketing Analyst

September 2017 - November 2017 (3 months)

Researched and provided insights on relevant subject area and developed a 360 degree marketing program.

social ambassador

September 2017 - November 2017 (3 months)

Work from home

Helped in promoting Qrius through various platforms.

Education

Kamala Nehru College

Bachelor of Commerce, Economics · (2017 - 2020)

St. Anthony's Senior Secondary School

· (2003 - 2017)